qango.com 2002-06-03

# Qango Info - Privacy Policy

Home : Company Information : Privacy Policy  

**Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy for the Qango.com Search Network

Qango.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices: 

Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website, produce statistical visitor data reports, and to protect you and us from security breaches of our servers, programs or files. 

Emails Automatically Sent

We use several programs that automatically send you an email when we update, change, remove or classify/reclassify your information. These emails are generated by our software and relate to any listing you may have submitted for inclusion or actions you may have taken with regard to your mailing list subscription status, or forum profile or postings. Occasional emails are sent from other programs for information purposes only and these usually do not require a reply or response. 

Advertisers

We use a variety of internal and external advertisement resources and companies to display ads on our sites. Some of these ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Forms

Some of our site's registration forms require users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address, etc). Contact information from the registration forms is used for a variety of purposes, e.g.; to ship purchases, to send information about our company, etc. We do not distribute, sell, exchange or otherwise propagate your email address to any other party. 

Contests

We occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). We do not distribute, sell, exchange or otherwise propagate any of this information to any other party, other than to use a limited reference to the data for mutually beneficial promotional purposes. Should anyone feel their information has been published by Qango.com in an unsuitable or incorrect manner we will make every effort to correct any mistakes or misunderstandings (See contact details). 

External Links

Qango.com contains links to other sites. Qango.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Public Forums

Qango.com makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Security

Qango.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Should there be a breach in our security we will work to repair any damage done, speedily and immediately upon discovery or notification. We will also endeavour to identify and take action against any person or entity that may be held accountable for such incidents. 

Contact Details

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Qango.com, or your dealings with us, you can contact us by email at [webmail@qango.com](mailto:webmail@qango.com) or by using our online form, here: http://info.qango.com/company/contact/index.html

< Back
